Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Ooh!
♪ 哦！
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
♪ SpongeBob
Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤！ ♪
♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
♪ 如果是航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants!♪Ready?
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪ 准备好了吗？
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants!
♪ 海绵宝宝！
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
Good morning, pineapple.
早上好，菠萝。
Good morning, Gary.
早上好，加里。
Good morning, world.
早上好，世界。
I'm ready!
我准备好了！
World?
世界？
Talk to me.
跟我说话。
Package, sir.
包裹，先生。
Ah-ha!
啊哈！
I can't believe
it's finally here.
我不敢相信
它终于来了。
There you go.
就这样吧。
Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
哦，谢谢你，
谢谢，谢谢。
Thank you, Mr...
Tennis Balls.
谢谢您，先生...
网球。
That's "Tentacles."
那就是“触手”。
Squidward's last name
is "Tentacles"?
章鱼哥的姓氏
是“触手”吗？
Poor guy.
可怜的家伙。
Hey, check out
Squidward's new snail.
嘿，看看
章鱼哥的新蜗牛。
Fancy.
想要。
So that's what came in the mail.
这就是邮件中收到的内容。
Looks like Gary has
a new little playmate.
看起来加里已经
一个新的小玩伴。
Dream on, SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝，梦想成真。
I wouldn't let Snellie here
play with that mongrel mutt.
我不会让斯内利在这里
和那只杂种狗一起玩。
She's a purebred.
她是纯种。
Wow. A snail made
out of bread.
哇。一只蜗牛做的
没有面包了。
No.
不。
Purebred means
she's of the highest pedigree.
纯种意味着
她的血统最高。
See?
看？
She even has her own papers.
她甚至还有自己的文件。
So if you'll excuse us
所以如果你能原谅我们
Snellie has to start
her training.
斯内利必须开始
她的训练。
Training?
训练？
For Bikini Bottom's snail race.
比基尼泳裤的蜗牛竞赛。
Snellie will be winning
this Sunday.
斯内利将会获胜
这个周日。
Sunday?
星期日？
Well, I guess I can't
enter Gary in that.
嗯，我想我不能
加里也加入其中。
Sunday's laundry day.
周日是洗衣日。
No, SpongeBob.
不，海绵宝宝。
You can't enter Gary
because Gary's a mutt.
你不能进入加里
因为加里是个杂种狗。
Boy, you got that right.
Gary's no...
男孩，你说得对。
加里不...
Hey! What makes you
so sure
嘿！是什么让你
如此确定
Gary couldn't win that race?
加里无法赢得那场比赛？
Papers.
文件。
Hmm, "Property of
Squidward Pimples."
嗯，“财产
章鱼哥痘痘。”
That's Tennisball...
Uh, Tentacles!
这就是网球...
呃，触手！
Come on, Snellie.
来吧，斯内利。
You know what?
你知道吗？
I'm starting to get the idea
我开始明白了
that Squidward thinks
his snail is better than mine.
章鱼哥认为
他的蜗牛比我的好。
No!
不！
Patrick, are you thinking
帕特里克，你在想吗
what I'm thinking?
我在想什么？
Yeah, I should get a snail
是的，我应该养一只蜗牛
and enter it
in that race and
beat Squidward.
并输入它
在那场比赛中和
击败章鱼哥。
Are youthinking
what I'm thinking?
你在想吗
我在想什么？
No, no, no!
不，不，不！
I'm thinking about entering
you in that race
我正在考虑进入
在那场比赛中的你
and beating Squidward's snail!
并击败章鱼哥的蜗牛！
Looks like we're going
看来我们要去
to start our training now,
ladies.
现在开始我们的训练，
女士们。
I call you a lady
to humiliate and demean you.
我称你为女士
羞辱和贬低你。
It's a motivational tool
we coaches use.
这是一个激励工具
我们教练使用。
Hmm, I don't know why
嗯，我不知道为什么
but I think I'll kick
SpongeBob's butt tomorrow.
但我想我会踢
明天海绵宝宝的屁股。
Kelp powder for muscle mass
海带粉增肌
raw eggs 'cause they're cliche
生鸡蛋，因为它们是陈词滥调
and nails for toughness.
和钉子以增强韧性。
Of course I expect you
to eat this.
我当然期待你
吃这个。
It's scientifically designed
to help you win tomorrow.
它是经过科学设计的
帮助您赢得明天。
Gary?
加里？
Wow, pretty good time.
哇，真是一段美好的时光。
Hey, SpongeBob,
check out my new snail.
嘿，海绵宝宝，
看看我的新蜗牛。
Patrick, your snail is a rock.
帕特里克，你的蜗牛是一块石头。
Yeah, thanks. I know.
是的，谢谢。我知道。
He's got nerves of steel.
他有钢铁般的意志。
See you at the big race!
大赛见！
Boy, the competition's
getting tough.
孩子，比赛的
变得强硬。
That's it, Gary.
就是这样，加里。
We are going to start
some serious training right now.
我们要开始了
现在进行一些认真的训练。
All right, Gary,
let's start with some sprints.
好吧，加里，
让我们从一些冲刺开始。
On your mark, set, go!
各就各位，出发！
Go, Gary, go, come on!
走吧，加里，走吧，来吧！
Go, Gary!
It's all yours, Gary!
走吧，加里！
都是你的了，加里！
Gary?
加里？
Come on, Gary,
the big race is tomorrow.
来吧，加里，
大赛就在明天。
You got to start training
if you want to win.
你必须开始训练
如果你想赢。
Don't waste your breath,
SpongeBob.
别浪费口气了
海绵宝宝。
That mongrel of yours
doesn't have a chance
against Snellie.
你那个杂种
没有机会
对阵斯内利。
Excuse me
打扰一下
but you two seem
to be forgetting
但你们两个似乎
被遗忘
who the real winner will be...
My snail.
谁才是真正的赢家……
我的蜗牛。
Patrick, that's a rock.
帕特里克，那是一块石头。
Yeah, thanks. I know.
是的，谢谢。我知道。
He's got nerves of steel.
他有钢铁般的意志。
Hey, what are you
standing on, anyway?
嘿，你是什么
无论如何，坚持下去？
Like I said
就像我说的
don't even bother
showing up tomorrow.
甚至不用打扰
明天出现。
My snail's really got Squidward
scared, huh, SpongeBob?
我的蜗牛真的中了章鱼哥
害怕吧，海绵宝宝？
Sorry, Patrick.
对不起，帕特里克。
Gary and I've got
some serious work to do.
加里和我有
一些严肃的工作要做。
You can run, but you can't hide,
Squarepants!
你可以逃跑，但你无法隐藏
方裤！
All right, Gary,
no more fooling around.
好吧，加里，
别再胡闹了。
Time to get serious.
是时候认真起来了。
Come on, Gary, move it!
来吧，加里，动起来！
Up, up, up, up!
Down, down, down, down!
起来，起来，起​​来，起​​来！
下来，下来，下来，下来！
Faster, faster, faster!
Go, go, go!
更快，更快，更快！
去！去！去！
Come on, push it, Gary, push it!
来吧，推吧，加里，推吧！
Move that shell!
移动那个壳！
Come on, Gary, move it!
来吧，加里，动起来！
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go! Faster!
我们走吧！我们走吧！
我们走吧！快点！
Let's go! Let's go!
Speed it up! Speed it up!
我们走吧！我们走吧！
加快速度！加快速度！
Move it, Gary!
Move it, move it, move it!
移动它，加里！
动起来，动起来，动起来！
Stroke, stroke, stroke.
中风，中风，中风。
Come on, Gary,
we're going to be late
来吧，加里，
我们要迟到了
for the big race!
为了大赛！
Good afternoon,
ladies and gentlemen
下午好，
女士们先生们
and welcome to our live coverage
欢迎收看我们的现场报道
of this year's spring classic,
the 102nd Running of The Snail.
今年的春季经典，
第102次蜗牛奔跑。
And what a beautiful day
for this sport of kings
多么美好的一天
为了这项国王的运动
of which I'm a huge fan.
我是其中的超级粉丝。
Seriously, I'm just a fan.
说实话，我只是一个粉丝。
I was on my way to my seat,
the door was open...
我正在走向座位的路上，
门是开着的……
Hey, what are you doing?!
嘿，你在做什么？
Sorry about that, folks.
抱歉，伙计们。
Let's go down to the field
我们到田野去吧
to join the mayor
for the pre-game ceremony.
加入市长
进行赛前仪式。
And now for the lighting of the
Torch of Good Sportsmanship.
现在是照明
良好体育精神的火炬。
Please join me
请加入我
in welcoming snail racing's
first-ever champion
在欢迎蜗牛赛跑的
有史以来第一个冠军
Lightning Larry Luciano!
闪电拉里卢西亚诺！
Would you look at that, folks?
各位，你们会看一下吗？
Lightning Larry Luciano,
a living legend
闪电拉里·卢西亚诺，
一个活生生的传奇
slowly making his way
center stage.
慢慢地走他的路
舞台中央。
And what a proud moment
for this sport.
这是多么值得骄傲的时刻
对于这项运动。
The crowd is going
absolutely nuts...
人群正在走
绝对疯了...
for Larry.
对于拉里.
He's almost there.
他快到了。
Uh, yes, siree.
呃，是的，长官。
Any minute now.
现在随时都可以。
He's almost a quarter
of the way there.
他快四分之一了
那里的路。
The torch is lit!
火炬点燃了！
Let the race begin.
让比赛开始吧。
Well, SpongeBob, I must admit
好吧，海绵宝宝，我必须承认
I didn't think
that mongrel mutt of yours
我没想到
你那只杂种狗
would even find
the starting line.
甚至会发现
起跑线。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
Save it for the loser's circle,
Squidward.
留到失败者的圈子里，
章鱼哥。
Gary happens to be
in the best shape of his life.
加里恰好是
处于他一生中最好的状态。
I'll alert the paramedics.
我会通知医护人员。
Good one, Squidward.
好一个，章鱼哥。
You guys ready?
你们准备好了吗？
Uh! A burglar!
呃！一个窃贼！
No, Patrick,
that's the official.
不，帕特里克，
那是官员。
We're ready to start
here, folks.
我们准备开始了
在这里，伙计们。
Okay, Snellie, let's show these
好的，斯内利，让我们展示这些
common, garden-variety snails
常见的花园蜗牛
what superior breeding
is all about.
什么优良育种
就是这样。
All right, Gary, listen up.
好吧，加里，听着。
The competition is
going to be fierce.
比赛是
会很激烈。
You're the undersnail.
你就是那只下蜗牛。
Everybody's already
counting you out.
大家都已经
算你了。
Now get out there and win
现在走出去并赢得胜利
so we can rub Squidward's
big, fat nose in it.
所以我们可以擦章鱼哥的
又大又胖的鼻子在里面。
This is what you've been
training for, Rocky.
这就是你曾经的样子
训练，洛基。
This is why we're here.
这就是我们在这里的原因。
On your mark, get set
各就各位，准备就绪
slither!
滑行！
And they're off!
他们走了！
Number six, Snellie, rockets out
of the starting blocks
第六名，斯内利，火箭出局
起跑器
leaving the other two
competitors in the dust!
留下另外两个
尘埃中的竞争对手！
What?
什么？
Go, Snellie, you got it, baby!
去吧，斯内利，你做到了，宝贝！
What are you doing, Gary?!
The race has started!
你在做什么，加里？
比赛开始了！
You let Snellie take the lead!
你让斯内利带头！
Let's go, Gary!
Start moving!
我们走吧，加里！
开始行动吧！
You're blowing everything
we trained for!
你毁了一切
我们训练的目的！
Blowing it!
吹了！
It's okay, Rocky.
You go when you feel like it.
没关系，洛基。
当你想走的时候你就走。
Gary, are you listening to me?!
加里，你在听我说话吗？
Get the anchors out
of your pants right now!
把锚拿出来
现在就脱掉你的裤子！
Don't give me that look!
别用那种眼神看我！
I said now, mister!
Get going, Gary!
我说现在，先生！
走吧，加里！
Go, go, go, go!
走，走，走，走！
And there goes number seven
out of the starting gate.
还有第七个
出了起跑门。
Hang on, folks.
坚持住，伙计们。
He doesn't look so good.
他看起来不太好。
Not good enough, Gary!
Not good enough! Faster!
还不够好，加里！
还不够好！快点！
I do not like the look of this.
我不喜欢这个样子。
Come on, Gary, it's a race!
A race!
来吧，加里，这是一场比赛！
一场比赛！
Have you heard of 'em?!
你听说过他们吗？
That coach is pushing that snail
too hard.
那个教练正在推那只蜗牛
太难了。
Faster, Gary! Faster, faster,
faster, faster!
快点，加里！更快，更快，
更快，更快！
Huh?
啊？
Oh! Looks like number seven
has a blowout.
哦！看起来像七号
有井喷。
Oop, make that two, folks.
哦，伙计们，做两个吧。
Uh, Gary?
呃，加里？
Plus a blown head gasket!
加上一个吹掉的头部垫圈！
Oh, and the poor creature's
still going for it.
哦，还有这个可怜的生物
仍在努力。
Um, Gary, you can stop now.
嗯，加里，你现在可以停下来了。
And he's losing control!
而且他正在失去控制！
You can take a breath now
if you want to, Gary!
你现在可以喘口气了
如果你愿意的话，加里！
He's spinning out of control!
他正在失控地旋转！
He's heading straight
for the wall!
他径直前进
为了墙！
No!
不！
Hold on, Gary, I'm coming!
加里，坚持住，我来了！
Whoa-oa.
哇哦。
One of the coaches seems
to have raced onto the track.
其中一位教练似乎
已经跑上赛道了。
That is an automatic
disqualification.
那是一个自动
取消资格。
Looks like number six
has this race all wrapped up,
看起来像六号
这场比赛已经结束了吗
ladies and gentlemen.
女士们，先生们。
Come on, Snellie,
it's all you, baby!
来吧，斯内利，
都是你，宝贝！
Oh, Gary, I'm sorry.
哦，加里，对不起。
Why didn't you just say
I was pushing it too hard?
你刚才为什么不说
是我逼得太紧了吗？
You did?
你做到了吗？
Oh, Gary, why didn't you tell me
I wasn't listening?!
哦，加里，你为什么不告诉我
我没听？！
You did?
你做到了吗？
Oh, Gary!
哦，加里！
What?!
什么？！
Gary?
加里？
Oh...
哦...
Aw...
噢...
My, oh, my.
我的，哦，我的。
Folks, I have never seen
anything quite like this.
各位，我从未见过
类似这样的事情。
It seems Snellie, the leader,
just went back to comfort Gary.
看来领导者斯内利，
刚刚回去安慰加里。
Looks like you and I are
in-laws, eh, Squidward?
看起来你和我都是
姻亲，呃，章鱼哥？
But that's impossible.
但这是不可能的。
If Snellie didn't win, then...
如果斯内利没有获胜，那么……
And the winner is Rocky!
获胜者是洛基！
I can't believe it.
我简直不敢相信。
My purebred...
Which cost me $1,700...
我的纯种...
这花了我 1,700 美元...
Lost to a rock.
迷失在一块岩石上。
Don't worry, Squidward.
别担心，章鱼哥。
I know how much
you wanted to win
我知道多少
你想赢
so I had the trophy
engraved to you.
所以我得到了奖杯
刻给你。
Gosh, Patrick, thanks.
天哪，帕特里克，谢谢。
"The 1st Place Snail Racing Cup
《蜗牛赛跑杯》第一名
Presented to
Squidward Tortellini?"
提交给
鱿鱼饺子？”
Will I ever win?
我会赢吗？
That's for yesterday,
Squarepants!
这是昨天的事
方裤！
You've got it tuned to KOLD...
您已将其调至 KOLD...
K-OLD, the all oldies station.
K-OLD，所有老歌电台。
Here's a little something
这里有一点东西
you may remember
from the good old days.
你可能还记得
从过去的美好时光。
♪ You're old
♪ 你老了
♪ You're old ♪
♪ 你老了 ♪
♪ Grumbling like a geezer
♪ 像个老头一样抱怨
♪ Yourself a-cracklin'
like an old has-been ♪
♪ 你自己噼啪作响
就像过去一样 ♪
♪ Look at yourself, old man,
you've got multiple chins ♪
♪ 看看你自己，老人，
你有多个下巴♪
♪ 'Cause you're old...
♪ 因为你老了...
Good morning, Daddy.
早上好，爸爸。
I made you breakfast.
我给你做了早餐。
Thank you, sweet pea.
谢谢你，甜豌豆。
I see you got creative
with the bran today.
我发现你很有创意
今天用麸皮。
Open up. It's time
for the pill.
打开。是时候了
为了药丸。
Oh, Barnacles.
哦，藤壶。
I hate the pill.
我讨厌药丸。
Ooh...
哦...
Pearl... do you think
I'm... old?
珍珠……你觉得
我……老了？
Well, of course I do!
嗯，我当然愿意！
But that's okay.
但没关系。
Daddies are supposed to be old.
爸爸们应该都老了。
But I'm still cool, right?
但我还是很酷，对吧？
Your old man is cool?
你老头子帅吗？
See, no one says "cool" anymore.
瞧，没有人再说“酷”了。
That's such an old-person thing.
这真是一个老人家的事了。
Now we say "coral," as in
现在我们说“珊瑚”，如
"That nose job is so coral."
“那个鼻子整形手术太珊瑚了。”
"Coral," eh?
“珊瑚”，嗯？
Ew. When you say it,
it sounds so uncoral.
呃。当你说出来的时候，
听起来很不道德。
What if I said it
with a different inflection?
如果我说了怎么办
有不同的变化？
Co-ral.
珊瑚。
Don't you have to go
to work or something, Dad?
你不必走吗
爸爸，去工作还是做什么？
Whoo! You're right.
呼！你说得对。
Have a coral day, honey.
亲爱的，度过珊瑚日。
Jenny, it's Pearl.
珍妮，这是珀尔。
Coral is definitely out.
珊瑚肯定已经出局了。
Ha! Old?!
哈!老的？！
What was I thinking?
我在想什么？
I ain't old. Huh?
我还没老啊？
Don't worry, Pops.
别担心，爸爸。
We're almost across the street.
我们快到街对面了。
Hey, get away from me.
嘿，离我远点。
I don't need no
snot-nosed little...
我不需要 没有
流鼻涕的小...
sorry you had to see that.
抱歉你不得不看到这一点。
Come on. Move it!
快点。移动它！
Could you be any slower?
你能慢点吗？
And you've had your blinker on
你已经打开了你的闪光灯
for the last five blocks.
最后五个街区。
Hey, Mister, could you
嘿，先生，你可以吗？
throw the ball back over here?
把球扔回这里？
Hey, how's about
I join you kids?
嘿，怎么样
孩子们，我加入你们吗？
Uh... that's okay.
呃……没关系。
You can keep it.
你可以保留它。
Why do old people always
have to ruin the fun?
为什么老人总是
一定要破坏乐趣吗？
Hey! No cutting!
嘿！不准切割！
You got to wait your
turn like everybody else.
你必须等待你的
像其他人一样转动。
No... no!
I ain't old like you!
不……不！
我没你那么老！
I ain't old!
我还没老啊！
What's his problem?
他有什么问题吗？
Next.
下一个。
Mommy, my Krabby patty
tastes funny.
妈妈，我的蟹黄饼
味道很有趣。
Well, no wonder.
嗯，这也不足为奇。
It's all old and dried out...
一切都又旧又干了...
like that man right there.
就像那里的那个人。
Now, put that thing
where it belongs...
现在，把那个东西
它属于哪里...
In the garbage.
在垃圾里。
♪ La-la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦，
啦啦啦啦♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la... ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦，
啦啦啦啦……♪
Well, little patty,
we're two of a kind.
嗯，小帕蒂，
我们是两个同类。
We've both lost our luster.
我们都失去了光彩。
Hmm. So that's
what I taste like.
唔。所以那就是
我的味道怎么样。
Good morning, Krusty Crew.
早上好，克鲁斯蒂·船员。
Hi, Patrick! You all ready
for the big night out tonight?
嗨，帕特里克！你们都准备好了
今晚的盛大夜晚？
Yeah, it's gonna rock!
是的，它会摇滚！
Are you ready to go crazy?!
你准备好疯狂了吗？！
I'm already hearing voices!
我已经听到声音了！
Are you ready to...
你准备好了吗...
SpongeBob! Patrick!
Do you mind?
海绵宝宝！帕特里克！
你介意吗？
Let's continue
this conversation
in private, Patrick.
让我们继续
这次谈话
私下里，帕特里克。
I think some people
are eavesdropping!
我认为有些人
正在窃听！
Well, how rude of some people!
唉，有些人真是粗鲁啊！
Mmm. Those youngsters
are going out
嗯。那些年轻人
正在外出
for a big night on the town.
在城里度过一个美好的夜晚。
Whoo! I've been looking
forward to this night all week.
呼！我一直在寻找
整个星期都期待着这个晚上。
Party!
派对！
What do you think
we should do first?
你觉得怎么样
我们应该先做什么？
What shouldn't we do first?
我们首先不应该做什么？
We're young...
我们还年轻...
we've got wheels...
我们有轮子...
the world is our oyster!
世界是我们的牡蛎！
SpongeBob, you got something
on your shoulder.
海绵宝宝，你有东西
在你的肩膀上。
Hey, boys.
Hanging out?
嘿，孩子们。
出去玩？
Yes.
是的。
I couldn't help
我无能为力
overhearing your big plans,
and I was wondering
无意中听到你的大计划
我想知道
if you had room for one more
crazy dude tonight, huh?
如果你还有空间再容纳一位
今晚这个家伙很疯狂吧？
Of course. Did you want
to come with us, Mr. Krabs?
当然。你想要吗
跟我们一起去吗，蟹老板？
Oh... hadn't even
crossed me mind.
哦...甚至没有
我突然想到。
But sure! I'll go!
但当然！我去！
I don't know, SpongeBob.
我不知道，海绵宝宝。
He might cramp our style.
他可能会限制我们的风格。
Style!
风格！
Let's see if he knows
让我们看看他是否知道
the secret cool-guy handshake.
秘密的酷人握手。
Uh... yeah!
呃……是啊！
'Course I know it.
我当然知道。
Uh...
呃...
I'm waiting... old man.
我在等……老头子。
Uh... how do you do?
呃……你怎么样？
Fine, and you?
All right, you're in.
很好，你呢？
好吧，你进来了。
But I'm not happy about it.
但我对此并不高兴。
You passed the test,
Mr. Krabs!
你通过了测试，
蟹老板！
Great! Why don't you boys
show up at my house at 8:00.
伟大的！为什么你们男孩不
8:00 出现在我家。
I just want to warn you,
Mr. Krabs
我只是想警告你，
蟹老板先生
we're always fashionably late.
我们总是时髦地迟到。
Hey, there, Mr. Krabs.
嘿，在那儿，蟹老板。
Are you ready to party!
你准备好参加派对了吗！
Oh, I'm ready to party!
哦，我准备好参加聚会了！
Are you ready to party?
你准备好参加派对了吗？
I'm ready to party!
我准备好参加派对了！
Are you ready to party,
SpongeBob?
你准备好参加派对了吗
海绵宝宝？
I'm ready to party!
我准备好参加派对了！
Are you ready to party,
Mr. Krabs?
你准备好参加派对了吗
蟹老板？
I'm ready to par-tay!
我准备好参加派对了！
Are you ready
to par-tay, SpongeBob!
你准备好了吗
来派对吧，海绵宝宝！
I'm ready to par-tay!
我准备好参加派对了！
Are you ready to par-tay,
Patrick?
你准备好参加派对了吗
帕特里克？
I'm ready to party!
我准备好参加派对了！
Are you ready to party,
Mr. Krabs?
你准备好参加派对了吗
蟹老板？
I'm ready to party!
我准备好参加派对了！
Are you ready to...
你准备好了吗...
Stop it!
Just stop it.
停下来！
停下来吧。
You're embarrassing me, Dad.
你让我很尴尬，爸爸。
So... what kind of hot rod
will we be cruisin' in tonight?
那么...什么样的热棒
今晚我们会巡航吗？
Only the most powerful
chick-magnet in town...
只有最强大的
镇上的小鸡磁铁...
the underwater heartbreaker.
水下的心碎者。
It's more like
a chick repellent.
它更像是
一种小鸡驱避剂。
And there's only two seats.
而且只有两个座位。
Calm your waters,
Mr. Krabs.
平静你的水面，
蟹老板。
I modified this little
baby myself.
我修改了这个小
宝贝我自己。
Are you sure this is what
the kids are driving these days?
你确定这是什么吗
这些天孩子们开车吗？
Only the cool kids.
只有酷孩子。
Hey. You guys
must be lost.
嘿。你们
一定会丢失。
Doofus Drive
is around the corner.
杜福斯大道
即将到来。
We're not lost.
我们没有迷路。
I've got my compass.
我有我的指南针。
So long, dorks!
Ha-ha!
再见，傻瓜们！
哈哈！
Good-bye, pals.
再见，朋友们。
We used to beat people up
for saying things like that!
我们曾经打过人
说出这样的话！
Everything's
all topsy-turvy now.
一切的
现在一切都乱七八糟了。
Here we are...
我们在这里...
The Wash.
洗涤。
They sure are giving these clubs
some crazy names.
他们肯定会给这些俱乐部
一些疯狂的名字。
I have to tell you boys...
我必须告诉你们男孩们...
I'm a little nervous.
我有点紧张。
I haven't been, you know,
"on the scene"
我没去过，你知道，
“在现场”
for quite a while now.
已经有一段时间了。
Just follow our
lead, Mr. Krabs.
只需关注我们的
领导，蟹老板先生。
And above all...
keep it cool.
最重要的是...
保持凉爽。
Cool... Gotcha.
酷...明白了。
Hello, gang.
SpongeBob's back.
你好，帮派。
海绵宝宝回来了。
Let's party!
让我们一起狂欢吧！
Any port in a stor...
商店中的任何端口...
Wait a minute.
等一下。
This is a Laundromat.
这是一家自助洗衣店。
Oh, yeah! Whoo!
哦，是啊！呼！
That's what I'm talking about.
这就是我要说的。
Oh, yeah, yeah!
哦，是啊，是啊！
The colors!
颜色！
Whoa, yeah!
哇，是啊！
You guys want another
rinse cycle? I'm buying.
你们想要另一个
冲洗周期？我正在买。
You know, I love staring
at delicates
你知道，我喜欢凝视
在熟食店
as much as the next guy, but...
和下一个人一样多，但是......
it's just that, I thought
we'd see more of the nightlife.
就是这样，我想
我们会看到更多的夜生活。
Something that will give me
能给我的东西
that wild and crazy,
hot-blooded feeling...
那样的狂野和疯狂，
热血的感觉...
if you know what I mean.
如果你明白我的意思。
Oh, I know what you mean,
Mr. Krabs.
哦，我知道你的意思，
蟹老板。
This is only stop numero uno
on our night of debauchery!
这只是停止 numero uno
在我们放荡的夜晚！
Debauchery!
放荡！
Debauchery? I never thought
放荡？我从没想过
of picking up trash under
the highway as hot-blooded.
捡拾下面的垃圾
高速公路同样热血沸腾。
But if it's what the kids
are into...
但如果这就是孩子们的事
进入...
So are you feeling
你也有这样的感觉吗
that wild and crazy
feeling, Mr. Krabs?
那样狂野和疯狂
蟹老板，感觉怎么样？
Not yet.
还没有。
Don't worry, you will.
别担心，你会的。
Are you feeling it
now, Mr. Krabs?
你有感觉吗
现在，蟹老板？
I'm feeling a warm spot.
我感觉有一个温暖的地方。
Sorry.
对不起。
Are you feeling it now
你现在有感觉吗
Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板？
Are you feeling it?
你感觉到了吗？
I'm feeling it, SpongeBob.
我感觉到了，海绵宝宝。
Patrick, that's not a ride.
帕特里克，那不是搭车。
Get off of me.
离开我。
Are you feeling it now,
Mr. Krabs?
现在你有感觉吗
蟹老板？
Are you feeling
it now, Mr. Krabs?
你有没有感觉
现在就可以了吗，蟹老板先生？
Art thou feeling it now,
Mr. Krabs?
你现在感觉到了吗，
蟹老板？
You feeling it now,
Mr. Krabs?
你现在感觉到了，
蟹老板？
Shh!
嘘！
How about now?
Can you feel it, Mr. Krabs?
现在怎么样？
蟹老板，你能感觉到吗？
Can you feel it,
Mr. Krabs?
你能感觉到吗，
蟹老板？
Can you feel it, Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板，你能感觉到吗？
Can you feel it,
Mr. Krabs?
你能感觉到吗，
蟹老板？
So, you want to know
if I can feelit?
所以，你想知道
如果我能感觉到吗？
Yeah! Yeah!
是的！是的！
Do you really want to know
if I can feelit?
你真的想知道吗
如果我能感觉到吗？
Yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah!
是啊是啊！是啊是啊！
Because I can feelit.
因为我能感觉到。
You want to know what
I'm feeling?
你想知道什么
我感觉？
Yes! Yes!
是的！是的！
I'm feeling like
a total barnacle-head!
我感觉就像
一个十足的藤壶头！
You think this is cool?!
你觉得这很酷吗？
How about this!
这个怎么样！
And this! Am I with it now?
还有这个！我现在同意了吗？
You guys wouldn't
know a good time
你们不会
知道好时光
if it bit you in the aft end!
如果它在尾部咬了你！
I'm going home.
我要回家了。
You guys ain't cool.
你们不酷。
You're lame!
你太蹩脚了！
Uh... lame?!
呃……蹩脚？！
Lame!
瘸！
You're nerds! Geeks
你们是书呆子！极客
Creeps! And babies!
令人毛骨悚然！还有宝贝们！
Not babies!
不是婴儿！
I may be old, but even
an old bag of shells like me
我可能老了，但即使
像我一样的旧贝壳袋
knows that you haven't suggested
one cool thing all night!
知道你没有建议
整个晚上一件很酷的事情！
So good night to ya!
祝你晚安！
I guess you're going to miss
the panty raid.
我猜你会错过
内裤袭击。
The what?
什么？
I said... I guess you're going
我说...我猜你会去
to miss the panty raid.
错过内裤袭击。
Panty raid? You're talking
about girls, right?
内裤袭击？你在说话
关于女孩，对吗？
Girl girls?
女孩女孩？
Yeah.
是的。
And you're talking
about raiding their dressers
而你正在说话
关于袭击他们的梳妆台
for their underpants, right?
为了他们的内裤，对吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Well, count me in!
好吧，算我一个吧！
If this works, I'll take
back what I said
如果这有效，我会采取
回复我说的话
about you two being lame.
关于你们两个瘸子的事。
Not lame!
不蹩脚！
Now, this is more like it!
现在，这更像了！
Give us some credit, old man.
老伙计，请给我们一些信任。
We're panty professionals!
我们是内裤专家！
We score here all the time.
我们一直在这里得分。
Frilly things!
褶边的东西！
We hit the jackpot!
我们中大奖了！
Oh, yeah,
Mr. Krabs!
哦，是的，
蟹老板！
Woo-hoo!
呜呼！
You finally came through
for me, boys!
你终于熬过来了
为了我，孩子们！
I feel young again.
我感觉又年轻了。
Eugene?
尤金？
Mother?
母亲？
What are you doing
with my bloomers?
你在做什么
和我的灯笼裤？
Well... I, uh...
嗯...我，呃...
Why didn't you tell me
this was my mother's house?
你为什么不告诉我
这是我母亲的房子？
Why didn't you ask?
你为什么不问？
Uh... ooh.
呃...哦。
But it was all SpongeBob
and Patrick's idea!
但这都是海绵宝宝
和帕特里克的想法！
Go to your room, mister.
去你的房间吧，先生。
You're grounded
for the rest of the night.
你被接地了
剩下的夜晚。
Yes, Mommy.
是的，妈妈。
Don't worry, pops.
别担心，爸爸。
We're almost to your room.
我们快到你的房间了。
Sorry, Mr. Krabs.
对不起，蟹老板。
Ah, that's all right, lad.
啊，没关系，小伙子。
I certainly feel younger.
我当然感觉自己更年轻了。
Good night, Mr. Krabs.
晚安，蟹老板。
Good night, SpongeBob.
晚安，海绵宝宝。
Eugene, lights out!
尤金，熄灯！
Yes, Mommy.
是的，妈妈。
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
cess Group at WGBHaccess.wgbh.org
cess 小组，网址：WGBHaccess.wgbh.org